<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:53:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering</title>
      <link>https://example.org/volunteering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/volunteering/</guid>
      <description>Want to volunteer? Scout Groups only exist due to volunteers, and we are constantly looking for fresh faces to join the team. If you would like to volunteer your time even if only occasionally for logistics in the background, then please contact us and we will be in touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform</title>
      <link>https://example.org/uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/uniform/</guid>
      <description>Uniform The simplest solution for uniform purchases is to talk to Squirrel/Beaver leader Rachael (Or your section Leader), who can explain what is required and give a rough idea on sizing. You can then pay directly for the uniform, and one of our members will put in the leg work to go and get it free of charge - it should simply be waiting for you at an upcoming meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrels</title>
      <link>https://example.org/squirrels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/squirrels/</guid>
      <description>Squirrels Ranging from ages 4-6 the Squirrel are the first step on the road of Scouting. With a range of of games and activities the aim is to spark curiosity and build the groundwork for life long skills.&#xA;Sessions run on Monday from 17:30 - 18:30 and subs are £2.50 per night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scouts</title>
      <link>https://example.org/scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/scouts/</guid>
      <description>Scouts Scouts are the oldest members of the 17th Group, with ages spanning 10½-14. More challenging/exciting activities are available for both members joining directly and those coming up from Cubs.&#xA;Sessions run on Thursdays from 19:00 - 21:00 and subs are £3 per night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/policy/</guid>
      <description>Website Policies Content To the best of our knowledge all content hosted on this website is either freely available or created by us. It should also be noted that while we endevour to strictly adhere to official Scout policy, all opinions expressed on this website are those of the person expressing them and may not necessarily reflect those of Scouting as a whole. If you have concerns on either point please get in touch and we&amp;rsquo;d be happy to address them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://example.org/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/news/</guid>
      <description>News One Lottery We&amp;rsquo;ve recently started a lottery via One Lottery which will help with Scout fundraising for the group. Each week has a guaranteed prize for one member of the group (amount based on signups) as well as a chance for the grand prize. If you wish to sign up you can do so on the One Lottery Website. If you have questions there is an FAQ page or you can get in touch with one of your leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://example.org/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/location/</guid>
      <description>Location Our headquarters can be found opposite St Bartholomew&amp;rsquo;s Church at the far end of the gravel car park.&#xA;We ask all visitors to contact us in advance, both for reasons of safety, and to make sure you are able to get access through the gate (there&amp;rsquo;s nothing worse than standing in the rain waiting for a Leader to check their phone).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explorers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/explorers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/explorers/</guid>
      <description>Explorers and Network Ages 14-18 for Explorers and then 18-25 for Network. These sections are run by West Leeds Scout District rather than directly by the 17th. When Scouts move up to explorers from the 17th we will put them in touch directly. Ideally they will move up in a small group and know a few of the young leaders (who are explorers themselves) so that they have familiar faces while they settle in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents</title>
      <link>https://example.org/documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/documents/</guid>
      <description>Documents Section Reports 2021&#xA;Section Reports 2022&#xA;Group Scout Leader&amp;rsquo;s Report 2023&#xA;Cycle Ride documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beavers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/beavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/beavers/</guid>
      <description>Beavers Beavers range from ages 6-8 and are introduced to more adventurous activities including overnight sleepovers. The Beaver group hovers around max capacity, so if you think your child(ren) may wish to join please get them on the waiting list ASAP.&#xA;Sessions run on Fridays from 18:00 - 19:30 and subs are £3 per night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubs</title>
      <link>https://example.org/cubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/cubs/</guid>
      <description>Cubs Cubs are slightly older than the Beavers spanning ages 8-10½. The majority of Cubs will have joined from Beavers, but there are places available for joining Cubs directly (there may be some delay depending on numbers).&#xA;Sessions run on Mondays from 19:00 - 20:30 and subs are £3 per night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Us Questions? Thoughts? Cookie recipes?&#xA;You can reach us at hello@17thswscoutsleeds.org.uk </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board</title>
      <link>https://example.org/board/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/board/</guid>
      <description>Group Trustee Board The Group Trustee Board members support the 17th Scout Group and are collectively charity trustees of the Group. Some of their responsibilities involve managing insurance, finances, property and assets of the Group - in short most larger administration matters. For a full outline of their responsibilities you can check the official Scout website Group Trustee page.&#xA;The Group Trustee Board consists of:&#xA;Ex Officio Members Roger Foyle (Group Chair) Helen Robinson (Group Secretary) Brian Schofield (Group Treasurer) Nick Ladley (Group Scout Leader) Elected Members Julie Greaves Louise Middleton Peter Whitfield Kevin Bird.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dates</title>
      <link>https://example.org/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/dates/</guid>
      <description>Dates for the Diary Monday 05 January First night of Cubs and Squirrels (Autumn term)&#xA;Thursday 08 January First night of Scouts (Spring term)&#xA;Friday 09 January First night of Beavers (Spring term)&#xA;Monday 16 February No Cubs or Squirrels (Half Term)&#xA;Thursday 19 February No Cubs or Squirrels (Half Term)&#xA;Friday 20 February No Beavers (Half Term)&#xA;Friday 27th March Last night of Beavers (Spring Term)&#xA;Monday 30th March Last night of Cubs and Squirrels (Spring term)</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
